At a strategic level, the primary way clients see value from Validatar is through building ongoing trust in the quality of data assets so that users of the data are able to use that data confidently in making important business decisions

At a tactical level, Validatar serves as the hub to enable all of the processes that are required to develop trust in data assets:
		Validatar serves as a catalog for all metadata related to data quality processes
		It serves as a central repository for tests that check the data so there is clarity about where and how to apply rules, checks and tests on data as well as where to see results over time.
		It automates the creation of data checks/tests saving time and effort that would otherwise be required to build those.
		It continuously monitors and alerts you if there are data quality issues that arise from the rules you have set up.
